<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://joseph.martinsen.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://joseph.martinsen.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-11-25T18:24:17-06:00</updated><id>https://joseph.martinsen.com/</id><title type="html">Joseph Martinsen</title><subtitle>Joseph Martinsen Personal Website</subtitle><entry><title type="html">WorldCorperate Games</title><link href="https://joseph.martinsen.com/photography/volleyball/2017/11/25/world-corperate-games/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WorldCorperate Games" /><published>2017-11-25T06:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-11-25T06:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://joseph.martinsen.com/photography/volleyball/2017/11/25/world-corperate-games</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://joseph.martinsen.com/photography/volleyball/2017/11/25/world-corperate-games/">&lt;p&gt;For more than 25 years the Games have placed unlimited opportunities within everyone’s reach around the globe. Over 170 Games have been held in great cities around the world since then. The 1st World Corporate Games was held in San Francisco in 1988. This year Houston hosted the World Corporate Games on November 17-19, 2017.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/wcg/wcg-1.JPG&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; alt=&quot;Post Sample Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/wcg/wcg-2.JPG&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; alt=&quot;Post Sample Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/img/wcg/wcg-3.JPG&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; alt=&quot;Post Sample Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Corporate Games are the world’s largest corporate multi-sport festivals open to everyone and to every size and kind of organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teams, tiny or tremendous, include employees, colleagues, family and friends and over 20,000 unique organizations have been represented in the Games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of the world’s most successful companies are keen supporters of the Games and its ideals. For example, Deloitte have entered more than 80 Games worldwide, Ernst &amp;amp; Young and IBM over 70 Games, KPMG and PWC over 60 Games. Each year, more and more companies are realizing how the Games can help them and their staff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All sports, individual and team, are open equally to women and men with competition based on age. The Games encourages participation regardless of ability. The oldest competitor to date is 87.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Competitors wear the colors and logos of their organization and build confidence, loyalty and team spirit. Medals and Corporate Awards are presented to winning athletes and organizations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Games has been honored by the patronage of hundreds of great leaders and ambassadors such as Nelson Mandela, Francois Mitterand, HRH Princess Anne and Sir Alex Ferguson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health and Fitness in the workplace, teambuilding and networking are obvious key benefits, as is the significant economic impact and exposure for the Hosting Cities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of sponsors have worked with the Games to create brand exposure, develop new business opportunities and meet new clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every Games offers multiple benefits and unrivalled opportunities to Organizations, Cities, Participants, Licensees, Sponsors, Venues, Hotels, Restaurants, Students, Staff, Suppliers, Sports Federations and Organizing Committees, Officials, Charities, Business, and the Economy… the list goes on!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joseph Martinsen</name></author><summary type="html">For more than 25 years the Games have placed unlimited opportunities within everyone’s reach around the globe. Over 170 Games have been held in great cities around the world since then. The 1st World Corporate Games was held in San Francisco in 1988. This year Houston hosted the World Corporate Games on November 17-19, 2017. The Corporate Games are the world’s largest corporate multi-sport festivals open to everyone and to every size and kind of organization. Teams, tiny or tremendous, include employees, colleagues, family and friends and over 20,000 unique organizations have been represented in the Games. Many of the world’s most successful companies are keen supporters of the Games and its ideals. For example, Deloitte have entered more than 80 Games worldwide, Ernst &amp;amp; Young and IBM over 70 Games, KPMG and PWC over 60 Games. Each year, more and more companies are realizing how the Games can help them and their staff. All sports, individual and team, are open equally to women and men with competition based on age. The Games encourages participation regardless of ability. The oldest competitor to date is 87. Competitors wear the colors and logos of their organization and build confidence, loyalty and team spirit. Medals and Corporate Awards are presented to winning athletes and organizations. The Games has been honored by the patronage of hundreds of great leaders and ambassadors such as Nelson Mandela, Francois Mitterand, HRH Princess Anne and Sir Alex Ferguson. Health and Fitness in the workplace, teambuilding and networking are obvious key benefits, as is the significant economic impact and exposure for the Hosting Cities. Hundreds of sponsors have worked with the Games to create brand exposure, develop new business opportunities and meet new clients. Every Games offers multiple benefits and unrivalled opportunities to Organizations, Cities, Participants, Licensees, Sponsors, Venues, Hotels, Restaurants, Students, Staff, Suppliers, Sports Federations and Organizing Committees, Officials, Charities, Business, and the Economy… the list goes on!</summary></entry></feed>